// Image credits: Kickstarter
const cards =  [
    {
    id: 1,
    level: "Easy",
    question: "What is the 2nd planet in the solar system?",
    answer: 'Venus',
   
    
    },


    {
    id: 2,
    level: "Easy",
    question: "What is the satellite of the earth?",
    answer: 'The moon',

    },


    {
    id: 3,
    level: "Easy",
    question: "What is the 8th planet from the sun?",
    answer: "Neptune",
    },


    {
    id: 4,
    level: "Medium",
    question: "Can we live on Mercury planet?",
    answer: "The harsh conditions on the planet's surface and the tenuous atmosphere make it impossible for any life form known to man to exist",
    },


    {
    id: 5,
    level:  "Medium",
    question: "Can humans breathe on Mars?",
    answer: "Mars does have an atmosphere, but it is about 100 times thinner than Earth's atmosphere and it has very little oxygen",
   
    },

    {
    id: 6,
    level: "Medium",
    question: "Is Mars hot or cold",
    answer: "Mars is generally considered a cold planet, with average temperatures that are much colder than Earth's",
    
    },

    {
    id: 7,
    level: "Medium",
    question: "Is Uranus full of diamonds?",
    answer: "Yes. High pressure experiments suggest large amounts of diamonds are formed from methane on the ice giant planets Uranus and Neptune",
    
    },

    {
    id: 8,
    level: "Hard",
    question: "What gas makes up the majority of Jupiter's atmosphere?",
    answer: "The gas that makes up the majority of Jupiter's atmosphere is hydrogen (75%)",
    
    },

    {
    id: 9,
    level: "Hard",
    question: "What is the name of the largest and most well-known ring system surrounding Saturn?",
    answer: 'It is is the "A ring" or the "Outer Ring".',
   
    },

    {
    id: 10,
    level: "Hard",
    question: "What is the name of the spacecraft that orbited Saturn from 2004 to 2017?",
    answer: 'It is is the "A ring" or the "Outer Ring"',
    
    }

   
]


  
  export default cards;